zaffingo.com 2018-06-29

# Zaffingo - Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy describes the policies and procedures of Zaffingo on the collection, use and disclosure of your information when you use the website. We will not use or share your information with anyone. 

**Information Collection and Use**

Zaffingo uses information we collect only for account creation and book-making purposes.

**User-Provided Information**

You provide us information about yourself, such as your name and e-mail address, if you register for a member account with the Service. Your name and other information you choose to add to your profile will not be available for public viewing on the Service. We may use your email address to send you Service-related notices (including any notices required by law, in lieu of communication by postal mail). We may also use your contact information to send you marketing email messages.

If you use your Facebook, Twitter, or other social networking site ("SNS") account information to sign in to Zaffingo, we will collect and store your SNS user ID, and other information that you explicitly allow us to access when using an SNS login.

**Information Collected Automatically**

We use automated technologies to collect and analyze certain types of information we consider to be non-personal information, including: (a) information related to the devices you use to access or interact with the Service, such as: IP addresses, geolocation information, unique device identifiers and other information about your mobile phone or other mobile device(s), browser types, browser language; and (b) information related to the ways in which you interact with the Service, such as: referring and exit pages and URLs, platform type, the number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed and the order of those pages, the amount of time spent on particular pages, the date and time you used the Service, and other similar information. We may also capture other data, such as search criteria and results.

**How We Share Your Information**

We are an early stage business and don't share your information with anyone at all.

**How We Protect Your Information**

Zaffingo uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial, and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to Zaffingo or guarantee that your information on the Service may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards.

In the event that personal information is compromised as a result of a breach of security, Zaffingo will promptly notify those persons whose personal information has been compromised, in accordance with the notification procedures set forth in this Privacy Policy, or as otherwise required by applicable law. 

**Links to Other Web Sites**

We are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from the Service, nor the information or content contained therein. Please remember that when you use a link to go from the Service to another website, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other website, including those that have a link on our website, is subject to that website's own rules and policies. 

**Changes to Our Privacy Policy**

If we change our privacy policies and procedures, we will post those changes on this page to keep you aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we may disclose it. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.
